Hello friends, my name is Sachin, and
today I'm back with a video, not a text.
So friends, today we're going to talk about the
SBI General Insurance's
Supreme Policy. Friends,
I've already made an audio-video about this plan,
but I told you that this
plan comes in three variants.
What we'll do is we'll make videos of all three variants one by one. I've
already
made videos of two variants. The
first plan is the plan, with a time limit ranging
from ₹300,000 to ₹500,000. The
second plan is the Plus, with a
time limit ranging from ₹600,000 to ₹200,000. The
third plan, with premium
options, ranges from ₹2,500,000 to
₹50 million. So friends, I've already
made a video of the problem. If you want to
see videos of both, I'll
write them in the description. You
can go there and watch them. In this video, I'll
discuss the premium plan. So, let's
start our review of this bank.
First, let us find out how much
time is available here. Friends, this is a very long
term plan. Those who want to take a fixed amount of Rs 25 lakh, 30 lakh, 35 lakh,
40456, 1 crore or even Rs 5 crore,
can take it under this plan. Friends, till now I have
not seen a single plan of any company worth Rs 5 crore, but it is
available here. Talking about free and post-graduation,
friends, here the
expenses of the plans above seven days and up to 180 days
are available here. Friends, free means
when you were not admitted in the hospital, the
doctor had done some tests for you, the
doctor had given you some medicines, the doctor had done
some starch on you, so
such expenses due to hospitalization are
called pre-hospital additional expenses. Similarly,
when you are discharged and
come home and after that the doctor has done
some medical tests for you, some medicines for
food or the doctor has
taken some consultation fees from you, so whatever
bills there are here, all these  Fingers will be drawn.
Talking about the room rent limit,
friends, there is no room rent
limit here. You can take rooms of any category,
be it the category above Sweet Heart Suite
or any other because this is the High
Sameshwar plan. Earlier, there used to be
private rooms like singles in both the plans,
but there is no room rent limit in this plan.
Same with ICU limit, friends, there is no
limit on the issue here.
Whatever is there here, the hospital will take your age
charts, whether it is 10,000 per day,
20,000 cheque or 25,000 cheque, then
you will get the full amount here.
Whatever is celebrated here will be given to you.
Look, talking about treatment,
friends, there are 537 such procedures
which are covered under day care.
Suppose sometimes you have to undergo cataract surgery,
suppose sometimes you have to undergo kidney
surgery, then friends, these are such
treatments. Here you do
not need 24-hour hospital operation. You are
admitted in the morning chapter.  In the evening, when you
return home after being discharged, you will be
given this cashless procedure here.
Friends, if you want a list of this, you
can ask me for it by WhatsApp or emailing me. I will give it to
you at the end of the day. Talking about the no-claim
bonus, friends, here
you will get a no-claim bonus of 15% every
year. Suppose you have taken a
policy of 1 crore here, then next year,
15 lakh rupees will be added to yours
and this goes up to a maximum of 100%, that is, the sum assured of
1 crore will
gradually increase and reach 2 crore rupees.
Talking about alternative treatments, friends, these are treatments
which are different from allopathy,
such as Ayurveda, Siddha, Unani,
Praveen. Friends, if you are given these treatments during treatment, if you are
given treatment with these medicines, then that
is also covered under this policy. Now,
leaving aside the facilities, if we talk about the benefits, friends, then
here it is a very unique benefit.
200% benefit is available here.
Suppose you have taken this policy of ₹10000000
and here your hundred percent gets
exhausted within a year, then the company will make
₹10000000 available to you here again within the same year. Besides,
it
also works on Same Pasand and Shameless, but
between the two, friends, it
is necessary to have knowledge of 45 days and the best thing is
that the refill starts first
and for example, suppose you have
taken a policy of Rs 1 crore and your first claim
comes for Rs 1000000, then
your refill benefit will get triggered, so
now in that year, instead of Rs 90 lakh,
you will have Rs 1 crore plus 90 lakh, that is, up
to Rs 1 crore is available. If suppose your
claim comes within this limit, then the
claim here will be given to you.
Moving ahead, friends, now let's talk about organ
donor expenses. Friends, there are many such
situations.  It happens that sometimes you have to
take a kidney as donation from someone,
you may or may not get a liver donation or any other
body donation, so friends, if any
donor here gives, then his
expenses will also be covered, the
donor is his owner, he will be treated, the
organ will have to be removed from his body, it will have to be
harvested in your body, so all the
expenses of this donor will be
covered till submission,
friends, talking about ambulance cover, in this plan you get
hospitalization cover for Rs. 7000, the good
thing is that there is no maximum limit here
that you can claim one lakh rupees in a year, you
can claim up to Rs. 7000 for every hospitalization, friends,
talking about MB Jhala entry limit, friends,
here any healthy person from 18 years to 65 years
can buy this policy, after 45 years there is
a mandatory medical here, here it may happen that
you may get a telephonic medical,
you may be sent to some place
But after 45 years, the doctor
definitely discusses with you here.
Talking about newborn baby, friends, if you have
already taken a policy and
a child is born in your family, then
friends, if you have become a resident of 191 countries, then you
can add them in this policy and in the same
way, the age of this dependent child is
maximum up to 25 years, which is the maximum you can
keep the child under this policy.
Friends, if I talk about Thomas Alva Edison, then he is also
covered till the time of death, so what are the two
categories, let me tell you a little bit
that if suppose a patient is in
such a situation that he cannot be taken to the hospital,
he cannot go at all or there is no
room available in any of the hospitals near you, then
friends, in such a condition, if you are
giving him treatment at home, a
tracking doctor is coming there, a
nurse is visiting there,
you have provided hospital-like facilities to that patient there, then
this is your category  It
comes to Mission Hospital. The minimum
treatment here should be for three days.
If your patient goes beyond that, then
you should not worry.
You
can get all these expenses covered by the company during hospitalization. Talking about HIV and AIDS,
friends, this is also a
very unique feature in this policy. Till now, in the policies that I used to
see, HIV and AIDS were
not fully covered in it.
Sometimes there was a sub-limit, sometimes it was
not available. But in this policy,
friends, review meeting is available
provided that this disease has happened to you
after taking the policy. If you
already have it, then you will not get that cover here.
Friends, if we
talk about psychiatrist cover on maintenance here, then that is also
available till the end of the sub-limit. But there is a
ten percent sub-limit here and the
maximum is Rs 50,000 on some listed conditions
or not. If suppose there are any listed
conditions and this
claim is taken under it, then the maximum you will get here is only up
to Rs 50,000.  You will get a
play. Talking about genetic resources,
friends, yes, that is also covered here.
Genetic resources are there, friends.
For example, suppose your grandfather had a disease, it got
transferred from him to your father, from him it got
transferred to you, and it is
possible that the disease may also come in your future child. So, such
diseases which run from generation to generation are
called genetic disorders, so friends,
they will also be covered here. The
cost of this will be up to a maximum of Rs 21 lakh. Let's move
ahead, friends. Now let's talk about
internal conservator label whiskey. Friends, these are
such diseases which are congenital
and they are on the inside, meaning
like someone having a hole in the heart or
someone being born with another disease or some other
such diseases which are not visible to us from outside
but are with them since birth.
So friends, such diseases are also covered here up to
25 percent of the time.
Suppose, if you have taken a policy of Rs 1 crore, then
here the cover for
internal disease is up to ₹2500000.  It will be covered as well as
friends, there are some
advanced treatments here, there are some specific
procedures, I have sent you the list of
these 12 such procedures here, they will be
covered up to 25 percent of the time,
as you must have seen nowadays balloon
surgery is very famous, it is a very
modern treatment and chemotherapy, that is,
now instead of giving cancer medicine through radiation, it is
given to you through a midwife, that is, through a pill, its cost is quite high, so
friends, that is also covered here and robotic
surgery because it is being used a lot these days,
it is covered here, similarly
stem cell therapy, this is a very advanced
treatment, friends, it is covered here,
moving ahead friends, let's talk about health checkup, friends,
health checkup
is also available here, but it is after one year,
you will not get it in the first year, from next year, there are
some of these tests, you will
go to your diagnostic center and get
all these tests done there, the company will
not charge you any money, it is cashless,
help chart will be taken from you on 20
If I talk about bariatric surgery,
friends, then that too is available here till submission.
Friends, what is bariatric surgery?
Suppose, those who have taken the policy,
their weight increases a lot, it is very
much, they start having problems and the
doctor says that if your weight keeps increasing in this manner, then
you may have to undergo many more, so
for this you have to undergo bariatric
surgery, friends, this is an abdominal
surgery where the fat in the
stomach area is reduced, due to this the
weight reduces a lot, but this should be done
at the railway station of the doctor only,
so friends, this is also available here till the time of injury.
Talking about cataract cover,
friends, there will be a waiting period of two years for it,
so that is also available here.
₹1 on this, means you will
get a plan of one lakh rupees. If there is a
cataract in both the eyes,
then you will
get a cover of up to two lakh rupees here.
Talking about cataract recovery benefit, friends, that is
here.  An addition of Rs. 15000
is available if your hospital stay is more than a few days,
meaning if
you are admitted in the hospital for 10 days, 11 days or 12 days, then along with the
company, you will be given an extra
debasement of Rs. 15000
because they know that there are
some other expenses in the treatment which
you have to clear, so on this basis the company will
give you an extra Rs. 15000 debasement. Talking about the ambulance cover,
friends, it
makes a lot of difference, here only Rs. 10 lakh
is available separately for the ambulance, meaning if you have
taken a policy of Rs. 1 crore or for 25 lakh or have
chosen anything else here, then
you will get this ambulance cover of Rs. 10 lakh under this policy.
Talking about this, friends, it may happen that
many times wherever you are taking treatment
and the doctor has suggested some surgery or
some treatment for you, you are
not satisfied with it, then you can do it here.  You
can take an unlimited time policy
from the SBI General Insurance doctor. If you
feel that the doctor's opinion is absolutely correct, then
you can also accept his opinion. So,
a setting has opened here which you
can take from the SBI doctor. Compassionate Visit.
Hello friends, that is also very good. This is a
unique point here. Friends, what happens is that
sometimes such a situation arises that you have gone
out of the city or it is possible that
many members of your family have gone out there and
there is an accident or
they get sick and you have got them
admitted in the hospital of that other city. If
this hospitalization is more than the required time, then
you will have to pay a maximum of
Rs 20,000 here, excluding the time limit. So friends,
according to this policy, the maximum amount that will be covered here will
be Rs 20,000. Here,
air tickets worth up to Rs 20,000 will be
reimbursed for to and fro travel.
This is a very good point.
Friends, talk about its long term policy discount.
If you take a 2-year policy
in one go, then  You will
get an additional discount of four percent. Also, if you
buy this three-year plan in one go, the
company will give you a six percent discount on the total premium.
Moving ahead, friends, let's talk about
some of the benefits. Till now,
you will get all the benefits that you have, these are inbuilt features in the plan,
but
for these don't benefits, you will have to pay some extra money.
You can add this to your friends' account. So,
first of all, if I talk about it,
here is Delhi Hospital Cash.
Friends, it is available to you from ₹500 to ₹5000. It
is also available here for five to 45 days. You
can take it in any of the terms. Suppose you chose to buy for
thousands but you took it for 15 days.
Suppose your plan is for
more than 15 days, 16 days or
17 days, then you can take it here for a maximum of 15 days.  That is,
which is Rs. 15000, so
if you have taken the benefit, then the company will
reimburse Rs. 15000 extra to your account. Talking about the Major Relax Benefit,
friends, there are 30 such diseases here
which
come under the category of diseases, like,
suppose cancer, heart attack or
brain stroke, paralysis, then there are
34 such diseases, friends, you
can ask for it, here if any such disease
occurs, then you will be given this lump sum benefit,
suppose you have taken this benefit, you have
bought a policy of Rs. 25 lakh,
you have bought a house with this benefit maximum of Rs. 25 lakh and
you are diagnosed with any such disease, then
₹ 2500000 will be deposited in your account and whatever treatment
expenses you were supposed to get from this policy, you will definitely get it,
this is a donut feature, for this you are paying
extra money to the company, if we
talk about access somersault, then
friends,
this is also a very good feature if  Suppose
you have taken this policy and have
also added options for it, friends, the
options here are of one and a half times and two times,
suppose it is a policy of one crore and you have opted for one
and a half times, then here
your policy will work for one and
a half crore rupees in an accidental case by reducing the sum assured to one and a half crore rupees, in the
same way or if you
take two times or double the sum assured, then the
policy of one crore will
work for 2 crore rupees in an accident case, but for this
also you will have to pay a little extra, let's
talk about enhanced relative bonus,
friends, till now you have seen that
this policy is providing you a bonus of 15 percent,
whose maximum limit is 100 percent,
if you have
chosen the enhanced relative bonus option here, then
you will get a reduced relative bonus of up to 50%,
which will
go up to a maximum of 200 percent, which is quite a lot,
friends, if we
talk about no claim bonus, friends, no
claim bonus protector, then that
is also available here, if you consider any sum assured
above Rs 50,000  It remains below and if
you have taken this option then you will definitely get the no
claim bonus that you were supposed to get.
Now the no claim bonus will
not be deducted due to any reason. The option of co-payment
is also available here friends which is 10
percent and 20 percent but I would
suggest you not to take this because whenever
you take the co-payment option then whatever
bill you have taken in the co-payment, be it
10 percent or 20 percent, you will have to pay it on
your own.
Suppose someone comes here for Rs 10 lakh
and you have taken the payment option of 10 percent here then the
premium will be reduced from your side
but the bill of Rs 1 lakh,
you will have to pay it
from your own pocket because
if you have added Rs 10 lakh then 10 percent of it is 1 lakh. So
try to adopt this.
Talking about Anirudh Pred, friends,
it is
not even available here because within this policy
you are already getting rooms of every category, there is
no tapping of room rent.  With
this, if you look at the two planes that we have
seen at the back, you will find an option
available there. After taking it, you
can update the room in your hair's degree. Friends, there
is also a deductible option here. Friends, let me
tell you how it works. There are
two options in this, of 10,000 or 25,000.
If you think that I can pay the
first bill of 10,000 or 25,000 from my pocket,
that is my
capability, then the bill will be
settled only after that, that is,
you have taken the option of 25 thousand. Suppose your
bill comes for 5 lakhs, you have to pay Rs. 25,000 first. The
remaining 4 lakh 75 thousand will be
presented by the company. By taking this option,
friends, the benefit to you will be that
your cost will reduce to a great extent.
It is up to you which one you want to take, whether to take it
or not. Friends,
I will tell you a little about the expressions,
but from that  First, let me
tell you that I'm quite active on social media.
If you want to connect with me on Facebook,
you can search for Insurance Sachin.
Friends, we've created a group on Telegram
where you'll get the latest information on insurance, including
new product launches,
changes made by Idea, and the current situation in the insurance industry.
You'll
get all the latest information there. If you
want to connect on Instagram,
you can also connect with Insurance Sachin.
Similarly, you can follow me on Twitter as
Iswaran Sachin.
This is my WhatsApp number. If you have
any questions or want to share your documents,
you can ask them here. If you
want to write something down or
ask me something, you
can also email me here. Let's move on,
friends. Now, let's talk about Explore. There will be a
meeting period here
if you have a pre-existing condition, for example,
you have acidity, diabetes, thyroid
problems, or
cholesterol.  If you have had any problem with this, then
any such disease which you declare
that you already have, then here
friends, it will be covered after four years,
you will not get its power from the ribbon for
2 years, so friends, there is a waiting period here
like cataract, hernia,
joint replacement, stones, sinus,
nasal polyp, uterus
removal and some stomach problems,
so friends, these are some such problems which occur over a
period of time, they are not formed in a day, so
friends,
like every policy, here also there is a waiting period of about 2 years, after
2 years
you will see this policy,
friends, the waiting period is of 30 days, here
you will not get cover for any disease,
except accident, so if
you are hospitalized due to accidental injury, then
this policy will
work like this, friends, here there is a
special waiting period of 90s, suppose you have hypertension, heart
disease and rabbit and related questions
After purchasing a policy, if hypertension, heart disease, diabetes
reduces, then also you will have to wait for it as
I have mentioned here, only after that
this policy will work, that is,
from the day you bought the policy till Noida,
you will have to wait. Talking about the major reverse
benefit, friends, as I
told you that the company will give you a lump sum amount, there is a don't
benefit, so here there is a
waiting period of 200 days for 90s, like in
Noida, you saw the batting plate here
also, for example, suppose there is a heart attack or
cancer, then
it should not happen within the first 90 days, if it happens then
you will not get the benefit, along with this,
there is a survival waiting period of 30 days, that
means if you get this disease then you will have to
wait till 30 days.  It is important to live, it is
important to laugh, if this does not happen then
you will not get this cream.
Friends, if we talk about configuration, then its
waiting period here is also 15 days. Suppose you have
taken the policy today, after 15 days if
something happens and you are hospitalized due to it, then
you will get its
claim here. For more information,
if you want more experience in this, then
you will have to read the policy details,
I will give you the link of it
in the description, I will give you the link of the brochure
in the description, you can go
there and download and read it. So, I
hope
you have understood this plan, if you still have
any questions, then you can ask me on WhatsApp,
you can write me an email, I will definitely answer all your questions.
Friends, if you liked this policy, then do
not forget to share it with your friends. If you are new to my channel, then do not
forget to subscribe to it.
My name is Sachin Verma, I will meet
you in the next video.
Thank you very much for watching this video.